# Bianca Regulski

Boston, MA • 727-307-5403 biancaregulski.com biancaregulski@yahoo.com linkedin.com/in/bianca-regulski

Highly driven and innovative full-stack software engineer with three years of professional experience designing, building, testing, and deploying software solutions in Ruby on Rails, React, Python, and Java.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Validity** • Boston, MA • Software Engineer

JANUARY 2021- JANUARY 2024

- Led the development and deployment of an upgraded version of an email verification REST API, adding pagination features and meticulous error handling, with robust automated unit and integration testing, improving response times and ensuring continuous uptime for tens of thousands of users.
- Implemented the front-end and back-end of an inter-account credit transfer system in Ruby on Rails, improving organizational efficiency and speed by automating work that was previously handled manually by non-technical employees.
- Integrated Validity's email validation API into a widget in the Salesforce app, with automatic importation of Salesforce accounts in Validity's internal account system, increasing Validity sales among Salesforce users

# **Validity** • Boston, MA • Co-op Software Engineer

SEPTEMBER 2020 - DECEMBER 2020

- Collaborated with a large team to migrate a legacy codebase from VB .NET to Java Spring/React, resulting in faster performance, modernized user experience, and Mac compatibility.
- Enhanced front-end design by developing responsive UIs with a focus on intuitive navigation and optimized website performance.
- Optimized loading times for Liquibase queries with indexing, resulting in decreased page loading times by 30% for APIs pulling large numbers of records.

## **PROJECTS**

## Park Finder

- Developed web app in Python and React that calculates and displays the optimal parks between two addresses based on transportation time.
- Utilized Google Maps API for both calculating the midpoint coordinate on the back-end and displaying interactive map with responsive pins on the front-end.

### **SKILLS**

Ruby on Rails | Python | Java | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | TypeScript | React | SQL | Git

#### **EDUCATION**

Florida State University • Tallahassee, FL

AUGUST 2016 - MAY 2020

Bachelor's in Computer Science · Minor in Philosophy